http://www.motoventures.com/legal/

Search:
Privacy and Use Policy
MOTOVENTURES understands your concern with privacy and the collection and use of your personal information while visiting or interacting with the MOTOVENTURES Website. This document describes the policy of MOTOVENTURES regarding information received about you during visits to the MOTOVENTURES Website. The amount and type of information which we receive depends on how you use the site. Products shown may include options or other installed accessories. Specifications are based on information available at time of writing, subject to change without notice and may differ in each sales area. Contact MOTOVENTURES for more information and pricing.
This Online Privacy and Use Policy was last updated on 10.16.2008. For future updates to this Online Privacy and Use Policy please book mark this page and check back or send an e-mail to info@motoventures.com with the words “requesting notification of privacy policy updates” in both the subject line and body of the email.
Limitation on Scope of Content
The MOTOVENTURES Website contains information regarding MOTOVENTURES and its products and promotional programs. The MOTOVENTURES products described in this site contain uniquely American specifications and equipment and are offered for sale only in the U.S.A. (excluding Hawaii). Any promotional programs described in this site are available only in those states and territories of the U.S.(excluding Hawaii, Guam and Puerto Rico) specifically referred to within the description of the program. Any pricing information referred to in this site is in U.S. dollars.
The policies described in this Online Privacy and Use Policy do not apply to MOTOVENTURES’s offline communications, data collection practices, or other activities.
No Representation or Warranty
MOTOVENTURES reserves the right to modify the information contained in this site at any time without notice. While MOTOVENTURES makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that all material on this site is correct, accuracy cannot be guaranteed and MOTOVENTURES does not assume any responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of any information contained in this site. This site, and all information and materials contained herein, are provided to you “as is” and without warranty of any kind. This site may contain hypertext links to other World Wide Web sites which are completely independent of this site. MOTOVENTURES makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of the information contained in any such hypertext link, and any hypertext link to the World Wide Web site of another person or entity shall not in any manner be construed as endorsement by MOTOVENTURES of such person‘s or entity‘s World Wide Web site, products or services. Your linking to any other off-site pages or other sites is at your own risk. Your confidential use of this site cannot be guaranteed by MOTOVENTURES. MOTOVENTURES shall not be responsible for any harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality with respect to your use of this site or any information you transmit to this site.
Normal Website Usage
If you visit MOTOVENTURES‘s Website to read product information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. The information that we collect does not personally identify you and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are browsing, we may collect the following information: the type of browser and operating system used, the IP address, the date and time you access our site, the number of times you have accessed our site, whether your computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, application and plug-ins, the pages you visit and if you linked to motoventures.com from another website, the address of that website. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to better provide you with a smooth and efficient experience in using our website.
We use Google Analytics for aggregated, anonymized website traffic analysis. In order to track your session usage, Google drops a cookie (_ga) with a randomly-generated ClientID in your browser. This ID is anonymized and contains no identifiable information like email, phone number, name, etc. We also send Google your IP Address. We use GA to track aggregated website behavior, such as what pages you looked at, for how long, and so on. This information is important to us for improving the user experience and determining site effectiveness. If you would like to access what browsing information we have – or ask us to delete any GA data – please delete your _ga cookies, reach out to us via this form, and/or install the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to an individual‘s hard drive for record-keeping purposes so that we may track site and user activity. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most major Websites. By showing how and when visitors use the site, cookies help MOTOVENTURES to determine better which areas of our site are popular and which areas are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of our site will not function properly if you do so.
Surveys
Periodically, we may request visitors to provide information and feedback in the form of surveys. These surveys are voluntary and the visitor always has the option to decline. Any information collected will be used to evaluate the products and services of MOTOVENTURES.
Collection of Personally Identifiable Information to Provide a Service or Correspondence
There are instances where MOTOVENTURES requests and collects information which may be personally identifiable to provide the website visitor a service or correspondence (e.g., The “Contact Us” form, the “Sign Up” form, promotions, mailed brochures, and/or quick quotes). This personal information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, type of request, and possibly additional information, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data, and may be passed on to our dealerships and fulfillment associates. Once our dealers or fulfillment associates receive this information that data also becomes the property of the dealers or fulfillment associates. Any request to opt out of future communications from such dealers or fulfillment associates must be made to the dealers or fulfillment associates directly.
Transmission of Information
Transmission of information through our website can be unstable, unreliable and insecure. MOTOVENTURES makes every effort to ensure the secure collection and transmission of sensitive user information using industry-accepted data collection and encryption methodologies such as SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) and PGP (Pretty Good Privacy); there is a risk however, that information may be intercepted illegally.
Promotional E-mails
We may occasionally send out promotional e-mails as a service to our visitors. We send e-mails only if the user has opted to receive communications from MOTOVENTURES through its website.
Google reCAPTCHA
Our use of Google reCAPTCHA is only used to fight spam and abuse on our website. Your use of reCAPTCHA v3 is subject to the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Copyright/Trademark Ownership
This site © MOTOVENTURES. You may use the information, text or graphics contained in this site only for your personal use and may not reproduce, adapt or publish it, in whole or in part, for any purpose without the express written consent of MOTOVENTURES. The MOTOVENTURES mark and design are registered trademarks of MOTOVENTURES. The MOTOVENTURES mark and design may not be used, downloaded, copied or distributed in any way without the express written consent of MOTOVENTURES. These images are © MOTOVENTURES 2008. All rights reserved.
No Offer to Sell or Buy; Consent to Terms of Online Privacy and Use Policy
All of the information contained in this site is for information purposes only and in no way constitutes an offer to buy or sell MOTOVENTURES products. The purchase of any MOTOVENTURES product shall be subject to the terms and conditions of the applicable sale, lease or retail installment contract. By using this site, you signify your assent to the MOTOVENTURES Online Privacy and Use Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to change any part of the MOTOVENTURES Online Privacy and Use Policy. If you have questions or comments regarding the MOTOVENTURES Online Privacy and Use Policy, please contact info@motoventures.com and note Privacy and Use in the Subject line of the e-mail or contact us via mail by sending a letter to MOTOVENTURES Privacy Team, PO Box 403 Aguanga, CA 92596
Search:
